Welcome to Hannity and tonight the state of America,
the Democratic Party is a
nationwide embarrassment.
Their policies,
they are god-awful,
they're terrible,
their views extreme,
their rhetoric disgusting,
and their tactics are
cringeworthy at best.
And then to make matters worse,
in this off-year election
they're sending in candidates that are woke,
a joke,
and they all want all of
their constituents to be broke.
The leading candidate for mayor of New York,
a rabid communist anti-semite,
won't even call for the terrorist organization
Hamas to disarm.
How gutless.
Take a look.
Do you believe that Hamas should lay down
their weapons and leave the leadership in Gaza?
I believe that any future here in New York City is one
that we have to make sure that's affordable for all,
and as it pertains to Israel and Palestine,
that we have to ensure that there is peace,
and that is the future that we have to fight for.
But you won't say that Hamas should lay down
their arms and give up leadership in Gaza?
I don't really have opinions about the future
of Hamas and Israel beyond the question of
justice and safety.
We all know he believes in global antifada.
Now,
across the country,
the top Democrat running to be governor,
Katie Porter of California,
might be the single most unlikable person in America.
That's saying a lot.
I can think of a lot of people that are not
that likable after getting caught on tape
berating reporters,
her own staff,
and pretty much anyone else that comes into her line
of sight.
She is now suggesting that even more bad
behavior could soon be coming to light.
She knows she's been mean a lot more than what we know about.
Take a look.
Should California voters feel confident
that there aren't any more Katie Porter videos out there?
Well,
what I know is that I could have done better in those moments.
I'm going to be focused on earning their votes.
Ah,
send in the videos to Hannity at something.com.
I don't have an email.
Anyway,
back east in Virginia and New Jersey,
both Democrats running for governor are now
embroiled in their own scandals.
The polls are tightening dramatically in New Jersey.
Mikey Sherrill won't even commit to not raising
taxes even in higher—in one of the highest
tax states in the entire country.
Oh,
and she won't tell the people of New Jersey why
she was not allowed to walk with her
class at graduation at the Naval Academy.
I would
think inquiring minds in New Jersey
might need an answer to that question.
In Virginia,
Democrats there are becoming,
well,
the party of death and misery thanks to their support
for state-assisted suicide and their nonchalant
response to their—a candidate for attorney
general,
you know,
the guy that once called for his
political opponents and their children
to be murdered.
And meanwhile,
the Democrats' 2024 presidential nominee back on a book tour
reminding everyone why she lost in a landslide,
because she was so great.
Take a look.
Well,
some people have actually said I'm—I was
the most qualified candidate ever to run
for president.
I like your—I like the some people say.
Very nice.
But go ahead.
I'm just speaking
fact.
Oh, really?
OK,
coming up,
we're going to have a full rundown of this dumpster fire
now burning hot inside the Democratic Party.
But first, let's turn our attention to the
Democratic dumpster fire that is Capitol Hill.
Last night, they filmed themselves making a
lot of noise,
heroically marching to Speaker Johnson's
ceremonial office inside the Capitol.
By the way, he wasn't there.
Take a look.
Swear her in!
Swear her in! Swear her in!
All right.
Other than a desperate ploy for attention,
no one really seems to know what their goals were.
Speaker Johnson, as I said, wasn't there.
The House, they already passed a bill to keep
the government open.
In reality,
it's Senate Democrats that are now responsible for the
shutdown, hence the name the Schumer shutdown.
And tonight, they are still blocking Republicans
and other Democrats from getting the 60 votes
they needed to pass a continuing resolution.
Now,
they certainly won't be opening the
government before their radical base is taking
to the streets all around the country
for massive protests all weekend,
like the summer
of 2020. Why would the Democrats ever alienate
what is now their extreme radical voters?
They
can't win without them.
So they never would dare criticize them.
That's why they didn't
criticize them.
They won't stop.
They shouldn't stop.
And we're not going to stop supporting
the rioters,
you know,
hurling bricks and rocks at and Molotov cocktails at cops and
killing people and looting stores and billions of property damage.
But that's not stopping House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries,
Israeli leader in name only,
for waxing poetic about his noble cause.
Take a look.
House Republicans shut the government down.
Then they ran out of town.
And for the last three weeks,
they're nowhere to be found.
What more can I say?
You deserve better.
Oh, you deserve better.
They actually had a vote in the Senate
yesterday and they already did it in the House.
So we are clear.
Here's a list put together by the
Speaker's Office detailing the Democrats
actual demands to open the government.
Apparently,
they will only reopen the government if they get
a whopping 200 billion of your tax dollars
for health care benefits for illegals.
They also want
permanent emergency Obamacare covid subsidies.
Remember, they were supposed to be temporary.
Five hundred million for PBS and NPR. Four
million to LGBTQ democracy grants in the Balkans.
Two million
for feminist democratic principles in Africa.
Not sure what that means.
They want 1.5
trillion total in new spending to open
the government for a whopping seven weeks.
And tonight,
in order to get their way on all these issues,
Democrats,
they are ready and willing to sacrifice
paychecks of our brave men and women in the
military and millions of other government employees,
something that they said was so
reckless and irresponsible many times.
In fact,
according to an Axios report,
Democrats are calling Trump's efforts to pay our troops
during the shutdown illegal.
OK,
make no mistake,
Democrats have totally lost the plot in an effort
to resist Trump, placate their radical base.
They champion what?
The men's rights to play women's
sports and be in women's locker rooms.
So-called rights of illegals like a brego carcia,
you know,
over your family's safety and security.
They still cling to this deep fund,
this mantle,
no bail idiocy.
Oh, and reimagine the police.
They voted for the largest tax cut in the history of our country.
Rather,
they gave us the largest tax increase in history.
Now, this is not just my opinion.
No,
Democrats are now hemorrhaging support ahead of the midterms.
And when their own liberal networks and supporters are,
you know,
blaring sirens, maybe they should pay attention.
Take a look.
If you go back six months ago,
you go back to April,
Kate Baldwin,
what were we looking at?
Well,
we were looking at the Democrats with a very
clear shot of taking control of the U.S.
House of Representatives according
to the Cauchy prediction market odds.
We saw them at an 83% chance.
But those odds have gone plummeting down.
Now we're talking about just a 63% chance,
while the GOP's chances up like a rocket.
Democrats are not gaining the way that we expected.
Then you add in the fact that the state legislators
are adding potentially more GOP seats
like they've already done down in Texas,
like they've done in Missouri.
And then you add in the potential gutting of the VRA,
and all of a sudden,
it becomes much more difficult
for Democrats to gain.
All right, but it does get worse for Democrats.
A foolish plan from Newsom and other party
leaders to squeeze out a few more Democratic
seats from an electoral map already heavily
gerrymandered in favor of Democrats.
That is
now backfiring also in a major way.
Take a look.
If you offset California and Texas,
Missouri and Utah,
North Carolina and Maryland,
everything
left over is an advantage to Republicans.
And don't forget,
the Supreme Court is considering
what could really be the end of the Voting Rights Act,
which would protect minority groups.
So you don't have a state
that's half black,
for example,
that elects only one congressional member,
and everybody else goes to the Republicans that
would represent that population in some ways.
So if that is gutted,
Democrats could lose 19 seats.
This would be a huge amount.
I don't want anybody to ever get overly optimistic.
You know what?
Elections matter.
Your vote matters.
This midterm,
it is a tipping point for the country.
All progress will stop or it will continue.
And we'll talk a lot about it in the next year to come.
The numbers don't lie.
Cringeworthy political stunts.
They're not gonna save the Democrats from themselves.
This is now a radicalized party
with a radical socialist, even Marxist base.
They wanna upend our great American way of life.
And I fear dark days are ahead for anywhere in the country
where these people get elected.
Hey, Sean Hannity here.
Hey,
click here to subscribe to Fox News' YouTube page
and catch our hottest interviews
and most compelling analysis.
You will not get it anywhere else.